-嘿 JB 你猜怎么着 -你应该知道这车是
- Hey, JB, guess what. - You know this is a manual
手动挡不是自动挡 对吧
and not an automatic, right?
让我歇会儿 行吗
Give me a break, will you?
天快亮了 我很累
It's almost dawn. I'm tired.
况且我在捍卫你自由的时候
And I don't do a lot of driving
也不经常开车
when I'm protecting your freedom.
我的自由之一就是嘲笑你的烂车技
Which includes the freedom to mock your bad driving skills.
-你们这帮损友... -你知道我们很爱你
- With friends like you guys... - Aw, you know we love you.
是啊 我们只是通过直击灵魂的嘲讽来表达对你的喜爱
Yeah, we just like to show it through soul-crushing ridicule.
是的
Yeah!
是么 那真是谢谢你了 兄弟
Yeah, thank you, man.
我精疲力尽了
I am wiped out.
JB 你的假期什么时候结束
JB, when's your leave over?
大概就是几天后吧 新一轮部署又要开始了
Uh, next deployment starts in a few days.
还是回家比较有意思
It's been fun being home, though.
我还觉得自己是刚回来呢
I feel like I just got back.
快止血 保持镇定 好吗
...stop the bleeding... just need to stay calm, all right?
会没事的
Gonna be all right.
会没事的 坚持住
Gonna be fine. Stay with me.
-她 她喘不上气了 -好了 我们会让你
- Sh-She can't breathe. - Okay, we're gonna get you
呼吸顺畅些 好吗
breathing again, all right?
-帮帮她 -你要保持这个姿势别动
- Help her! - You need to stay very still.
救救她
Help her!
你很快会呼吸顺畅的 相信我
This is gonna make it easier for you, okay?
现在 呼吸
Now breathe.
吸气 呼气
Breathe, breathe...
NCIS 第12季08集
声明：
本字幕仅作学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业用途 否则后果自负
==GA字幕组==
翻译：小白 米兰伯爵 清欢仰慕者 lynhoo00 补汤
校对：寂静流年 清欢仰慕者 师太 Jzc BDFZer 低落的蓉小张
大主教：补汤
英文字幕：elder_man
谢谢你把他带回家了 警官
Thank you for bringing him home, Officer. I promise
-我保证没有下次了 -McGee
- this will never happen again. - McGee--
我是怎么跟你说 从华盛顿纪念碑上
what did I tell you about throwing pennies
往下扔钢G儿那事的
off the top of the Washington Monument?
噢 Tony 说得好像你在那接着似的
Oh, Tony, if only you were there to catch them.
那我会这么接
I would catch them like this.
嗨 Tony
Hi, Tony.
你好 Burt中士
Hi, Sergeant Burt.
你们这么早过来干什么
So, what are you doing here so early?
来接人还是来送啊
Picking up or dropping off?
Abby和我一起用的早餐
Abby and I had breakfast.
就在
After...
-我去她家接她以后 -有意思
- I picked her up from her place. - Mmm.
早餐啊 你们吃了什么
Breakfast. What'd you have?
抱歉 我饿了
Sorry, I'm starving.
我想听你说说 解解馋
Thought I'd live vicariously.
你真的饿了吗 Bishop
You're hungry, Bishop?
她总是觉得饿
She's always hungry.
我是说 你可别被菜鸟那娇小玲珑
I mean, don't let the probie's tiny,
低调谦逊的外形骗了
unassuming frame fool you.
千万不要
No.
她会毫不留情地把你整个吃掉
She'll swallow you whole.
我不怕
I'm not afraid.
我不吃人 Tony
I'm not a cannibal, Tony.
也许这就是我们从没见过Jake的原因
Maybe that's why we never see Jake.
大概是她把他吃了
Maybe she ate him.
也可能是他比较忙
Or maybe he's just busy.
又或者你把他吃了 还配上蚕豆和意大利红酒
【注：《沉默的羔羊》中汉尼拔经典语录】
Or maybe you had him with fava beans and a nice Chianti.
Burt 你和Abby之间是怎么回事
So, Burt, how are things going between you and Abby?
我从来没遇到过她这样的女人 McGee探员
Never met anyone like her, Agent McGee.
很棒 她很棒
It's been great. She's great.
超乎寻常的棒
Beyond great.
似乎一切都
Everything has just been...
-很棒 -很棒
- Great. - Great?
就这个意思
Exactly.
我们一拍即合
We just click.
-你懂吗 -是啊是啊 我懂的
- You know? - Yeah. Yeah, I know.
那么 从一切都变得很...棒开始
So, how long has it been since everything
到现在有多长时间了
started being... great?
两个月了吧
A couple of months.
相差不多 大概就是两个月
Give or take, I guess.
天呐 我得去做安全简报了 我快迟到了
Oh, boy, I'm gonna be late to my security briefing.
我得走了 回见 各位
Gotta go. I'll see you guys later.
好吧 有时间再见 两个月先生
【注：电影《阿波罗13号》中经典台词】
All right. Catch you on the flip side, Mr. Two-months.
可怜的汉子
Poor bastard.
我还挺喜欢他 个子又高 人又老实
Yeah, I really liked him. Tall, quiet.
很有“万宝路男人”沧桑成熟的样子
Had a sort of Marlboro Man quality to him.
为什么你们两个说得好像
Why are you two talking about Burt
再也见不到Burt一样
like you're never going to see him again?
Burt哪儿去了
Hey, where's Burt going?
-两个月了 -明白了
- Two months. - Copy that.
拿上装备
Grab your gear.
一个士官死于疑似肇事逃逸
Petty officer killed in a possible hit-and-run.
解释下呗
Um, hello?
我是不是错过了什么
Did I miss something?
你有什么发现 Duck
What do you got, Duck?
除了清新的秋日空气
Besides the crisp autumnal air,
干燥的叶子散发出的橡木味儿
the scent of dried oak leaves
还有冬日老人敲响
and the knock-knock of Old Man Winter
自然母亲前门的声音吗
on Mother Nature's front door?
是的 除了那些
Yeah. Besides that.
恐怕是个悲剧
Tragedy, I'm afraid.
不过在这种情况下 我还是很高兴看到罪魁祸首是这条平坦光滑的公路
Though, in this instance, I'm glad the culprit is a slick road
而不是边看短信边开车的傻瓜
and not a foolish texting fatality.
我记得他们说是肇事逃逸
I thought they said hit-and-run?
当地警察说有个目击者
Well, local LEOs have one witness
似乎看到事故发生时一辆SUV加速开走了
who might have seen an SUV speeding away,
但相关描述非常粗略
but it sounds sketchy.
-死者呢 -士官
- Victim? - Petty Officer
John Blaney Hicks 他是本地人
John Blaney Hicks. He was a local.
从"温斯洛普"号军舰上休假在家
Home on leave from the USS Winthrop.
有两个朋友和他一起 都是平民
Had two friends with him, both civilian.
他们被紧急送往医院时状况很不好
They were rushed to the hospital in critical condition.
看起来是车失控了
Looks like he lost control of the vehicle,
撞到了那边的栅栏
took out a fence up there
接着翻滚下山
and did a triple gainer down the hill.
-有刹车滑痕吗  -有一条
- Skid marks? - One set,
从那边的路上延伸过来
leading off the road.
栅栏刺破了挡风玻璃
Fence post went through the windshield.
士官脖子上的伤口就是
Yeah, and the wound on the petty officer's neck
他失血而亡的原因
suggests that it caused him to bleed out.
这些纱布是哪来的
Where'd all these bandages come from?
我知道是怎么回事
I think I can answer that.
我在死者的伤口上
I found what appears to be cornstarch powder
发现了玉米粉
on the victim's wounds.
玉米 玉米可有很多用途
Cornstarch-- there's so many uses for cornstarch.
我记得我的表姐Beatrice能用橘子和玉米粉
I remember my cousin Beatrice used to make the best
做出最好吃的华夫饼
orange and cranberry muffins,
她每次都不让我多吃
she'd have me add just a pinch,
然后
and it...
呃 还有医用手套
Um, the medical gloves--
急救人员大概是想抢救他
the EMTs probably tried to save him.
但救护车20分钟后才到
But it took EMTs 20 minutes to get here.
那他们给死人贴纱布干嘛
Why would they bandage a dead man?
他们没有
They wouldn't.
我是Sherman Harper警官 来自费尔法克斯县警局
Sergeant Sherman Harper, Fairfax County PD.
我是特别探员Gibbs
Special Agent Gibbs.
谢谢你长途跋涉而来
Thanks for making the trek.
消防部门和医疗救护员没有碰过死者
Fire department EMTs didn't do a thing to your petty officer.
他们是接警后赶来 赶到时
They responded to a 911 call, when they got here,
他已经被包扎过了
he was bandaged up already.
他的朋友也一样
Same with his friends.
谁试图救他呢
Who tried to save them?
是她
She did.
现场急救员说当他们阻止时
First responders say she was holding a trach tube
她正扶着一个姑娘喉咙里的导气管
in the girl's throat when they pulled up.
她到底是谁
Who exactly is she?
驾驶证上显示她叫Anna Dillon
Driver's license says she's Anna Dillon.
她说她在一公里外看到一辆SUV快速经过
Says she saw an SUV bolt past her a mile back.
再往前开点儿 就发现了车祸现场
Got a little closer and found the wreckage.
她坚称除非有律师在场 否则绝不开口
Insists she isn't saying anything else without a lawyer.
得把她带回警局
Gonna bring her back to the station,
叫一个公设辩护律师过来
call a public defender.
为什么 她不是在救人么
Why, if she saved their lives?
无执照行医 Gibbs探员
Practicing medicine without a license, Agent Gibbs.
她既不是护士 也不是医生
She's not a nurse, a doctor,
更不是急救人员
nor an EMT.
她这么做可能会导致别人死亡的
She could've killed someone.
也许就是如此
Maybe she did.
我还有工作要做
Got a job to do.
我们也是
Yeah, so do we.
还不能做好事了 哈
No good deed, huh?
是啊 似乎是不能了
Yeah, doesn't seem right.
Non faciat malum,
ut inde veniat bonum.
善有善报
“Do not do evil
恶有恶报
in order that good may come.”
医护兵
Corpsman!
汇报情况
Talk to me.
John Blaney Hicks下士
Petty Officer Third Class
和朋友在一起 玩到很晚
John Blaney Hicks was out late with friends.
刹车痕迹显示 他的车滑出了车道不可避免地坠落
Skid marks indicate his car spun out and fatally crashed.
乘客是Mary LaFleur和Benjamin Koss
Passengers were Mary LaFleur and Benjamin Koss.
他高中时期的好伙伴
Buddies from high school.
Mary正在接受牙科保健员培训
Mary is training to be a dental hygienist.
Ben从事建筑工作 并且在当地上大专
Ben does construction and attends a local junior college.
这个女人当场对这三个人进行了急救
All three received in-field medical attention from this woman,
前海军医护兵Anna Dillon
former Navy Hospital Corpsman Anna Dillon.
Dillon觉得她自己看见了一辆SUV逃离现场
Dillon thought she saw an SUV leaving the scene,
但是不能够提供任何细节
but couldn't offer any details.
她到哪儿都带着她的医疗装备 跟Marcus Welby一样
【注：美国医疗剧里的主角】
Carries her medical kit in her car like Marcus Welby.
谁是Marcus
Marcus who?
海军医护兵没有行医执照
Navy corpsmen don't carry a medical license.
退伍回家后 她和平民没什么两样
Back home, she's no different than a civilian.
-但是她接受了训练 -还有战地医护经验
- But she's trained. - And has field experience.
但是如果你进行急救 就是不合法的
Yeah, but you can't legally help.
那样不对
That's not right.
你以为呢
Yeah, ya think?
是医院打来的
That was the hospital.
Ben Koss在ICU里醒来了
【注：重症监护室】
Ben Koss is awake in ICU.
DiNozzo 带上Bishop
DiNozzo, take Bishop,
去和他聊聊 看他记得什么
go talk to him. See what he remembers.
McGee 打电话给Harper警官
McGee, call Sergeant Harper.
告诉他 我们需要和Anna Dillon聊聊
Tell him we need to talk to Anna Dillon.
Duck 就来
Yeah, Duck, I'm on my way.
你的专业意见呢 医生
What's your educated opinion, Doctor?
我觉得情况十分明了
I think it's abundantly clear
他的左颈动脉
that his left carotid artery
被一块栅栏柱切断了
was severed by a fence post.
不 不是说他
Oh, no, no, not about him.
我是说Burt
I meant about Burt.
你觉得Abby的公园巡警怎么样
What do you think of Abby's park police sergeant?
Palmer先生 你最好多关心关心
Your time would be better spent, Mr. Palmer,
你自己的事情
concerning yourself with your own affairs.
哦 我就是这么做的
Oh, I'm doing that, too.
你知道的 Breena正处于装修模式
You know, Breena's in nesting mode.
家里工程不断
Constant projects around the house.
搬搬这个 刷刷那个 造个储藏箱
Move this, paint that, build a hutch.
我都不知道"储藏箱"是什么
I don't know what a hutch is.
"橱柜"的高大上说法
Fancy word for a cabinet.
有什么线索吗 Duck
What do you got, Duck?
我正在告诉这位准父亲
I was just telling our father-to-be here,
一根栅栏柱切断了死者部分颈动脉
that a fence post partially severed his carotid artery.
但是受到那样猛烈的撞击
Yeah, but with the impact,
我怀疑 他死前甚至不知道自己被什么击中了
I doubt he ever knew what hit him.
Anna Dillon试着止血
Anna Dillon tried to stop the bleeding.
Jethro 当我们切开他的胸腔后发现
Oh, Jethro, when we opened him up,
他内出血十分严重
his body cavity was filled with blood.
很明显 年轻的女英雄成功止住了
Apparently our young heroine was able to stop
体外流血
the external bleeding,
但是体内出血 已经没得救了
but internally, he was far too far gone.
酒精浓度
Alcohol level?
0.0
Zero-point-zero.
"冷静的像个法官一样"
“Sober as a judge.”
而且他没有
And his records show
痉挛或滥用药物的记录
no history of seizures or drug abuse.
从医学角度上 不能解释车祸的原因
There was no medical reasons for the vehicle to crash.
我不敢相信JB死了
I can't believe JB is dead.
Mary在哪
Where's Mary?
她正在准备接受手术
She's being prepped for surgery.
真是场噩梦
This is a nightmare.
所以 Ben 帮我们把这些拼凑起来
So, Ben, help us piece this together.
发生了什么
What happened?
一只鹿穿过马路 JB受到了惊吓
A deer run across the road? JB panic?
不 先生
No, sir.
JB十分冷静
JB was rock solid.
医生说你的记忆可能有一点混乱
The doctor said your memory might be a little fuzzy.
我的记忆没问题
My memory's just fine.
JB没有失去对车辆的控制
JB didn't lose control of the vehicle.
我们被另外一辆车撞了
We were hit by another car.
有人把我们撞到下了马路
Someone ran us off the road.
Anna Dillon说的是真的
Anna Dillon was telling the truth.
你看到另外一辆车了吗
Did you see the other car?
或是看到那个司机了
Or get a look at the driver?
有没有可能撞你们的是辆SUV
Is it possible that it was an SUV?
我记得...
I remember...
感觉到有东西击打到了后保险杆
feeling something clip the back bumper,
并且当我们旋转的时候 看到了那辆车的尾部
and seeing the-the rear of a car as we spun.
但是之后...
But after that...
对不起 我希望我可以提供更多线索
I'm sorry, I wish I could be more help.
你应经提供了很多帮助
No, you've done plenty.
医生说 如果不是某个女人
The doctors said if it wasn't for some woman
在车祸后过来帮忙...
who came to the crash...
我就不会在这儿了
I wouldn't be here.
没错
That's true.
她以前是个海军医护兵
She's a former Navy corpsman.
你知道我能上哪儿找她吗
You know where I can reach her?
我想说声谢谢
I want to say thank you.
费尔法克斯县监狱
Fairfax County Jail.
对Anna Dillon 我们还知道些什么
What else do we have on Anna Dillon?
她参与了两次在阿富汗的海军舰队医护兵行动
Well, she served two Fleet Marine Force Corpsman tours in Afghanistan,
因为战斗中的英雄行为 获得一枚铜星勋章
awarded a Bronze Star for acts of heroism under fire,
救了12个人
saved 12 lives,
额外执行了30次国内行动
and performed over 30 additional in-country procedures.
现在在华盛顿的学校系统里做警卫
Currently works in the DC school system as a janitor,
那里某种程度上也算是战场
which is kind of like a war zone.
车祸当晚呢
What about the night of the crash?
她刚下班
Uh, she'd just finished her shift.
车祸发生后马上到达现场
She arrived at the site moments after the collision.
就在那时 她看到一辆SUV加速逃逸
That's when she saw an SUV speeding away.
为什么她现在不在这儿 McGee
Why isn't she in here, McGee?
我打电话给Harper警官
Well, I called Sergeant Harper.
她仍然在费尔法克斯县警局受审
She's still being questioned by Fairfax County P.D.
去 打给他
Go, get him on the phone.
你知道的 老大
You know, boss,
根据Anna Dillon的口供
according to Anna Dillon's records,
她报了警 并在到达后立刻开启安吉星服务
【注：通用汽车子公司，为通用提供汽车安全信息服务】
she called 911 and used OnStar the second she got there.
Anna Dillon知道
Anna Dillon knew
她会惹上麻烦 但她还是这么做了
that she was going to be in trouble and she did it anyway.
McGee
McGee.
Anna被正式起诉了
Anna's being officially charged.
县公诉人正在路上
County prosecutor's already on the way.
当你想要出来的时候 叫我一声
When you want out, just let me know.
想聊聊吗 士官
Ready to talk, Petty Officer?
我还在等我的律师
I'm still waiting for a lawyer.
公共辩护人
Public defender?
别太期待
Yeah, don't hold your breath.
你是NCIS的人
Well, you're NCIS.
他们说 我也不能和你交谈
They'd tell me not to talk to you, either.
也许吧
Yeah, maybe.
所以
So?
所以...他们不会理解
So... they won't understand.
他们不知道你是谁
They don't know who you are,
不知道你做过什么
they don't know what you've done.
我们想要帮忙
We want to help.
我很高兴听到这个 但是太晚了 长官
Well, I'm glad to hear that, but it's too late, sir.
我打了911
I called 911.
我想要去帮那些孩子 但是其中一个死了
I tried to help those kids and one's dead.
但是因为你 有两个人活了下来
Yeah, but two are alive because of you.
应该有三个人活下来的
There should be three.
我犹豫了
I hesitated.
不能怪你自己
Can't blame yourself.
我到那的时候 他还活着
He was alive when I got there.
我离开的时候 他已经死了
He was dead when I left.
我知道我可以做的更多
I know I could have done more.
呃...
Uh...
坐下吧
Sit down.
为什么不跑呢 Dillon
Why not run, Dillon?
为什么代人受罪
Why take the fall?
我有想过
I thought about it.
但 你还是留下了
Yeah... but you stayed.
我必须留下
I had to.
我接受的训练就是这样
I'm trained to.
我必须得说 这不是我预期的未来
I gotta say, this is not exactly the vision I had for my future.
我和那些急救员唯一的差别是
Only damn difference between me and those EMTs
-我们开不同的车到现场 -对
- is the car we drove up in. - Yeah.
还有法律上的差别
And the law.
我接受过那些训练 你知道的
I have the training, you know that.
自从我离开军队
Ever since I got out,
没能找到那方面的工作
I can't get a single job in the field.
我一直存钱 想攻读医学院
I've been saving to go to medical school.
但即使我被释放了
But even if I'm cleared,
这件事还会记录在我的档案上 你觉得会有人要我吗
you think anyone will accept me with this on my record?
我和陆军空军的军医学习的东西一样
I learned the same as the Army and the Air Force medics,
但是因为某些原因 他们出来的时候起码是个急救员
and for some reason, they come out EMT-Basic,
他们救那些孩子就是合法的
and-and they could have legally saved those kids.
我怎么就犯法了呢
Why can't I?
特别探员Gibbs 知道自己在做什么吗
Special Agent Gibbs, what do you think you're doing?
她还没有因任何罪名被起诉
She hasn't been charged with a crime yet.
她被公诉人拘留了
She's being detained for the prosecutor,
-公诉人正在他路上 -不
-who's on his way. -No.
公诉人不来了
Not anymore.
-你打电话了 -不 不是我
- You make a call? - No, not me.
是东部地区律师协会打的电话
U.S. Attorney for the Eastern District.
我知道她以前是海军
I know she's former Navy.
JB也是个海军
JB was Navy, too.
我比你想象的更尊重这身制服
I respect the uniform more than you know.
但她不应该碰他们
But she shouldn't have touched them.
她应该等待别人帮忙
She should have waited for help.
等待
Waited?
等待 看着他们死
Waited and watched them die?
小姐 我不是说这么做是对的
Miss, I'm not saying it's right.
但你的确违法了
But you broke the law.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
你为什么不去找肇事者
Why aren't you looking for the person who caused this crash?
-这是场意外 -不 不是
- It was an accident. - No, it wasn't.
警官 听着
Sergeant, look...
我们都想解决这个案子
we all want to solve this case,
但我们需要她的帮忙
but we need her help to do it.
如果你想要询问她
You want to question her?
你在这儿询问
You do it here.
用我的办公室 想怎么做都行
Use my office, whatever you need.
这不是关于询问
This isn't about questioning.
这是关于做正确的事情
This is about doing what's right.
Mary LaFleur 车里的一个乘客
Mary LaFleur, a passenger in that car,
刚刚从手术室出来
just got out of surgery.
她可能瘫痪了
She may be paralyzed.
你的医护兵在车祸后移动了她
Your corpsman moved her after the crash.
我做的都是对的
I did everything right.
跟急救员说去
Talk to the EMTs.
你不能为此责备我
You can't blame me for that.
我认识Mary的父母
I know Mary's parents.
我必须要回答她遭受了什么
I have to answer for what was done to her.
你是想要答案
You looking for answers
还是想找人顶罪
or you looking for someone to pin it on?
你是个聪明的人 Gibbs探员
You're a smart man, Agent Gibbs.
我不会和你争论
I won't argue with you.
但是你知道这样做的结果
But you know where this is headed.
你不能改变法律
You can't change the law.
是的 我们不能
No, we can't.
但我们可以竭尽全力 据理力争
But we can fight like hell and we can try.
我不知道你来了 Gibbs
I didn't know you come here, Gibbs.
非常不错的一杯咖啡
Pretty good cup of coffee though, huh?
我们的小秘密 对吗
Our little secret, right?
对
Right.
再见 Norvell
See you, Norvell.
为什么你坚持在这里见我
Why do you insist on meeting me here?
别告诉我是因为这里的食物
And don't tell me it's the food.
好人
Good people.
诚实的人
Honest people.
饥饿的人
Hungry people.
这里的总会三明治非常不错
The club sandwich isn't half bad.
对你父亲的离世我感到很难过
I'm sorry about your dad.
他会非常乐意遇见你
He would've loved to have met you.
传言说他和他儿子一样有挑战性
Rumor has it he was as challenging as his son.
是的 嗯 只是保守说法
Yeah, well, there's an understatement.
我喜欢好的挑战
I like a good challenge.
前海军医护兵尽力拯救生命
Former Navy corpsman tried to save lives.
现在她面临司法指控
Now she's facing legal charges.
体系的缺陷
Flaw in the system.
体系需要完善
System needs to be fixed.
嗯 很多人都会同意
Well, a lot of folks would agree,
但我能帮你做什么
but what can I do to help?
她需要一个律师
She needs a lawyer.
Carrie 她需要一个好的律师
Carrie, she need a good lawyer.
她需要你
She needs you.
我们不会赢
We won't win.
我知道 但你可以减轻指控
I know that, but you can lessen the charges,
然后我们与之对抗
and we take the fight to them.
再然后呢
And then what?
然后你告诉我该去和哪些人谈判
Then you tell me the right people to talk to.
但现在...
But right now...
我们是她仅有的一切
we're all she's got.
在她为了她的国家奉献了一切之后
After what she did for her country,
她应该得到一些支持
she deserves some support.
好吧 你欠我一次
Well, you will owe me.
我又不是没欠过
Well, I've been there before.
薯条变好吃了
Fries have gotten better.
医护兵过来
Corpsman up!
按住这个 士兵
Hold this down, Marine!
好的 这个也按住
All right, hold this, too.
靠着我
Give me your weight.
医护兵
Corpsman!
你会没事的
You're going to be fine.
救救我
Save me.
Anna...
Anna
Anna?
嗯
Hmm?
非常抱歉
I'm sorry, um...
我们说到哪了
where were we?
说完了 只要在你的口供上签字就行
Finished, just need you to sign your statement.
嘿 老大
Hey, boss.
我们这里都结束了
We're all done here.
真希望我能记起更多关于SUV的事儿
Wish I could remember more about the SUV.
我没能帮得上任何人 哈
I'm not being much help to anybody, huh?
好了 我们最好快走
All right, we better get moving.
我们就要一路堵回费尔法克斯了
We're gonna fight traffic all the way back to Fairfax.
她留在这里
She's staying here.
美国地检只允许我们暂时...
The U.S. Attorney only granted us temporary...
好吧 她留在这里
Okay, she stays here.
"这些不是我们要找的机器人"
【注：《星球大战》著名台词】
“These aren't the droids we're looking for.”
那现在怎么办
So what now?
听着 我知道 你不喜欢交谈
Look, I get it-- you don't like to talk,
但是你能给我点暗示吗 好让我知道我们在做什么
but can you give me a hint as to what we're doing?
清理一些事情
Clearing some things up.
你好 Jethro
Hello, Jethro.
我该为英雄做点什么
To what do I owe the honor?
Duck 这是前医护兵Anna Dillon
Duck, Former Hospital Corpsman, Anna Dillon.
啊 同道中人
Ah, a kindred spirit.
我是Donald Mallard 前英国皇家陆军军医队
Donald Mallard, former RAMC.
我们需要看看这位海军士官
We need to see the petty officer.
当然可以
Oh, of course.
这边走
Right this way.
下士John Blaney Hicks
Petty Officer Third Class John Blaney Hicks.
Dillon医护兵认为他应该活着
Corpsman Dillon thinks he should have lived.
我明白
I see.
年轻人 下士在车祸发生
Young lady, the petty officer lost more blood
最初十秒内失血太多
in the first ten seconds after the crash
是无论如何都抢救不回来的
than ever could have been compensated for.
我犹豫了
I hesitated.
如果我能尽快 我...
If I was quicker, I...
唯一能拯救这个人生命的方法是
The only thing that could've saved this man's life
从一开始就不曾经历这场事故
is if he never got into the accident in the first place.
-但是我...  -你没让他孤独地死去
- But I... - You didn't let him die alone.
无论谁在场都只能做到那样
That's all anyone could have done.
正如我的指挥官在一场
As my commanding officer once said,
极度激烈的战斗后曾说的
after a particularly ferocious battle,
"你没开枪
“You didn't fire the shot,
"所以你不能把所有逝去的生命都归咎于自己
“so you can't blame yourself for those you lose.
你不可能救所有人"
You can't save everyone.”
Abbs 我们需要你的帮助
Abbs, we need your help.
告诉我们你有线索了
Please tell us you have something.
我有线索了
I have something.
等等 你说这话是不是因为我请求你这么说
Wait, did you just say that because I asked you to?
是的 但也因为我发现了线索
Yes. But also because I found something.
我们看看
We'll take it.
好的 我们从Ben Koss那知道
Okay, we know from Ben Koss
Hicks士官的车辆被追尾
that Petty Officer Hicks' vehicle was rear-ended.
车尾部没有留下油漆
There was no paint left behind
所以我不能追踪凹痕
and I can't trace a dent.
但是...
But...?
拜托接下来一定要有但是
Please say there's a but.
但是
There's a but.
等等 你说这话是不是因为我请求你这么说
Wait, are you just saying that because I asked you to?
行了 直接说重点
Please, just get to the point.
重点是有油漆留下 看到没
The point is there was paint left behind. See?
我只看到银色
All I see is silver.
是的 原始的银色
Well, the original
是266号银色
was Silver 266
而我们的入侵者是272号银色
and our intruder is Silver 272.
当灯光下打在
And when the light hits
附着金属斑点上的时候 显而易见
the additional metallic fleck, it's clear.
它们完全不一样
I mean, they're totally different.
好吧 只要相信我就好
All right, just-just trust me.
记得提醒我绝不要向你们咨询室内设计
And remind me to never consult any of you on interior design.
我们需要匹配与266号或者272号银色相符的车型
We need to match the model 266 or 272.
-可能去车管所 -这是种老式的颜色
- Probably go to the DMV-- - It's an old color.
目前在费尔法克斯县注册的车只有五辆
There's five currently registered in Fairfax County.
-干得好 Abby  -太棒了
- Nice work, Abby. - Sweet!
怎么了
What?
我知道你正考虑做什么
I know what you're thinking of doing
我只是想让你知道
and I just want you to know
我认为还为时过早
that I think it's premature.
好吧 McGee 我知道我们曾经...
Okay, McGee, I know that we used to...
我们不必多言 已经过去很久了
and we don't anymore, and it's been a long time.
但是 呃 这是一种隐私
But, uh, this is kind of private
而且某种意义上也不关你的事 所以
and sort of none of your business, so...
Abby 得了吧
Abby, come on.
如果我想和Burt分手 那是我的决定
If I want to break up with Burt, that is my decision.
现在 请走开 我有工作要做
Now, shoo-- I have work to do.
McGee 拜托
Oh, McGee, please!
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
嗯... 你闻到什么没
Mmm... you smell that?
车用机油
Motor oil?
就是它了
Nothing quite like it.
柴油燃料
Diesel fuel.
车轴润滑脂
Axel grease.
我喜欢
I love it.
怎么了
What?
你真奇怪
You're weird.
我能为您效劳吗
Can I help you?
Dave Lancellotti
Dave Lancellotti?
你们是谁
Who's asking?
海军罪案调查处
NCIS.
想问一下你的银色皮卡
Got a few questions about your silver truck.
它怎么了
What about it?
昨天有一起肇事逃逸
There was a hit-and-run yesterday
你的车正好符合描述
and your vehicle matches the description.
太疯狂了
That's crazy.
它已经被锁了一周 在后面
It's been locked up all week, around back.
我只用它来拖Bridget
I only use it to haul Bridget, here.
正如你看到的 我的姑娘还跑不起来呢
As you can see, my girl is in no shape for racing.
我们还是需要看看那辆车
We still need to see the truck.
没问题
No problem.
你了解赛车吗
You know anything about racing?
是的 我在赛车场长大
Yeah, I grew up at the track.
三个兄长
Three older brothers.
在我之前的生命里你去哪了
Where you been all my life?
她一直在打击犯罪
She's been fighting crime
和消灭恐怖分子
and ridding the world of terror.
更别提 她结婚了
Not to mention, she's married.
车呢 Dave
Where's the truck, Dave?
见鬼...
What the hell...?
我发誓它就在这儿
I swear it was here.
你昨晚在哪 Lancellotti先生
Where were you last night, Mr. Lancellotti?
在曼彻斯特酒吧
At the Manchester Pub.
有人偷了我的车
Somebody stole my truck.
是的 可能 或者没有
Yeah, maybe. Or not.
听着 打电话给酒吧
Look, call the pub.
Woody Ross是酒保
Woody Ross is the bartender.
他会为我作证
He'll vouch for me.
好吧 为你着想 我希望他确实能作证
Well, for your sake, I hope he does.
你应该吃点
You should eat.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
从发生这一切开始后 我还没有机会
I haven't had a chance to catch my breath
喘一口气
since this all started.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢你 Dillon
Thank you, Dillon.
最近很多人都不说谢字了
Not enough people have been saying that lately.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你从哪来
Where you from?
最初 呃 维吉尼亚海滩
Originally? Uh, Virginia Beach.
父母呢
Parents?
我爸爸是一个制造商代表
My Dad was a manufacturer's rep--
类似销售员
kind of like a salesman.
我妈妈是个护士
Mom was a nurse.
把女儿抚养得很成功
Raised their daughter right.
他们应该自豪
They'd be proud.
是的...是的 他们很自豪
Yeah... yeah, they were.
长官 我只想有个机会...
Sir, I just want a chance...
你知道 做我擅长的事
you know, to do what I'm good at.
当我看到这起车祸...
When I saw that crash...
那些孩子...
those kids...
所有想法都冒了出来
it all just kicked in,
我知道
and I knew...
我知道我必须去做
I knew what I needed to do.
你不得不这么做 医生
What you had to do, Doc.
你好
Hello.
Anna 这是Carrie Clark
Anna, this is Carrie Clark.
一位律师
A lawyer.
了解海军
Knows about the Navy.
了解你
Knows about you.
Gibbs探员把你发生的一切
Agent Gibbs told me all about you
都告诉我了
and about what happened,
我来这是帮助你的 如果你允许的话
and I'm here to help, if you'll let me.
嘿 你来得真早
Hey! You're here early.
早起的鸟儿有虫吃
I wanted to catch a worm.
你们整个上午去哪了
Where you been all morning?
你了解我的 早起的麦小鸟
Well, you know me, McEarly Bird Special.
我喜欢挑灯夜战 开夜车
I like to work late, burn the midnight oil.
我们核对了Dave Lancellotti的不在场证明
We ran down Dave Lancellotti's alibi.
告诉我他的不在场证明有问题
Please tell me it fell through.
一个叫Woody的酒保替他做了担保
Woody the bartender vouched for him,
就在他打了Bishop之后
right after he hit on Bishop.
有些事情不太对劲
Something isn't right here.
是吗
Yeah?
你有答案吗
You got an answer?
看这个 老大
Take a look, boss.
Dave Lancellotti是个半职业赛车手
Dave Lancellotti's a semi-pro racer.
他有一个网站和一些粉丝
He has a Web site and a bit of a following.
从评论区看 他在赛场上是个急性子
Judging by the comments section, he's a hothead on the track.
粉丝们在这里上传了六个斗殴视频
There's half a dozen fight videos here, posted by fans.
那个
There.
这就是Lancellotti
There's Lancellotti.
放开我 放开我
Get off of me! Get off me!
-你想干什么 啊 -暂停
- What are you thinking, huh? - Freeze it.
-你撞坏了我的车 -那是...
- You wrecked my car! - That is...
Ben Koss
Ben Koss.
车祸的幸存者之一
One of the survivors from the crash.
Lancellotti肯定有动机
Lancellotti certainly had motive.
那起事故
The accident?
我已经把知道的都告诉你了
I already told you everything I know.
另一起事故
Different accident.
我们说的是赛车场那次
We're talking about the racetrack.
你和Dave Lancellotti
What was the fight about
为了什么事斗殴
between you and Dave Lancellotti?
你觉得他和这次事故有关
You think he has something to do with this?
不清楚
Don't know.
每次在赛道上撞车后 Dave都会跟人斗殴...
Dave fights with everyone after a wreck on the track...
但除此之外 他是个不错的人 非常正派
but he's a decent guy otherwise; loyal to a fault.
那天只是没发挥好
Just not the best driver that day.
怎么说
How so?
当时赛道很开阔
Well, the track was wide open.
我正想着加速 就在这时
I was looking for a fast groove when,
Dave突然冒出来 撞了我的车尾
out of nowhere, Dave bumps my tail.
两辆车都失控了 撞向了外侧的围栏
We both spun out, hit the outside rail.
听起来很耳熟啊
That sounds familiar.
这太吵了
This is loud!
真的吗
Really?
开车回家的时候听这种音乐 你不会觉得很放松吗
You mean you wouldn't find this relaxing on the drive home?
嘿 你能把声音关掉吗
Hey, can you turn this down?
18英寸电子管 哥们
18-inch tubes, man.
那可是高端货
That's high-end stuff.
什么
What?
我能为你做些什么吗 宝贝儿
Can I help you with something, sweetheart?
NCIS
NCIS.
我们在找David Lancellotti
We're looking for David Lancellotti.
哦... 好吧 真伤心
Oh... well, that's too bad.
我倒希望你是来找我呢
I was kind of hoping you'd be looking for me.
不好意思 请问你是
I'm sorry. And you are?
Bennett Jamine 为您效劳
Bennett Jemaine, at your service.
什么事 两位
What's this about, guys?
Lancellotti在这儿工作 对吗
Lancellotti works here, right?
兼职 怎么了
Part-time. Why?
知道他现在在哪吗
Any idea where he is?
谁知道呢
Who knows?
在你们来找过他之后
Dave got kind of antsy-pantsy
Dave就变得坐立不安
when you guys paid him a visit.
哦 这个我们还是知道的
Oh, yeah, we know about that.
同事们都在议论
Co-workers talk.
你能进一步解释一下"坐立不安"吗
You want to go ahead and define “antsy-pantsy”?
当你们说Dave可能和那个海军小伙的
Upset a lot of people when you guys said Dave
死亡有关后 很多人都感到烦躁不安
might have something to do with the death of that Navy kid.
你不会恰好是昨晚在Manchester俱乐部
You wouldn't happen to be the female agent that got into it
与Woody发生争执的女探员吧
with Woody over at Manchester's Pub last night, would you?
呃 对 他不太喜欢我
Uh, yeah, he wasn't so happy with me.
我也许摔了几个装着花生的碗
There may have been a few peanut bowls thrown.
嘿 我不会介意那事
Hey, I wouldn't take that too personally.
听着 我们知道Dave的卡车不见了
Look, we know Dave's truck is missing.
如果你真想做个好朋友
You really want to be a good friend,
就把你知道的告诉我们
tell us what you know.
我最后一次见到Dave是在几小时前
Last time I saw Dave was a couple hours ago.
他说想一个人静静
Said he had to clear his head.
我就知道这么多
That's all I know.
嘿 我收到你的信息了
Hey, I got your text.
有什么事这么重要
What's so important it couldn't wait
不能等到你出了卫生间再说
until you were out of the bathroom?
你在说什么 我没有给你发信息
What are you talking about? I didn't text you.
-你发了 -是我发的
- Yes, you did. - I did.
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
你知道 男人才能进男厕所
You know, the “men” in “men's room”
这是个规矩不是个建议 菜鸟
is more of a rule than a suggestion, probie.
听着 你们俩经常一起说笑着来上厕所
Look, you two always get to go off giggling
而我却被扔在一边
to the urinal together and I always get left out.
所以我们要谈谈 而且要在这里谈
So we're gonna talk, and we're gonna do it here.
好吧
Okay.
但快点
But make it quick.
好
Okay...
你们俩知道Abby和Burt之间某些事
you two know something about Abby and Burt.
说说吧
Talk.
还记得吗 我曾经是国家安全局的人
Remember, I was NSA.
我知道怎么找出你们最不为人知的一面
I know how to find out your darkest secrets.
Gibbs有规定
Gibbs has rules,
我们都知道 但Abby...
we all know that, but Abby...
对约会有特别的要求
has ideas about dating.
Tony 这是秘密
Tony, it's a secret.
要真是个秘密 你们是怎么知道的
If it's so secret, how do you know about them?
这个问题问得好
That's a very good question.
我去守着门
I'll guard the door.
好吧...
All right...
你或许应该知道 我和Abby约会过
well, you should probably know that Abby and I used to date.
呃 相互喜欢的那种
Ew. Like, each other?
对
Yeah.
等等 这不是违背了第12条规定
Wait, isn't that a violation of Rule 12?
-不能和... -很久之前的事了
- Never date a... - It was a long time ago.
在我们分手之后的一个晚上 我去到她的实验室
After we had broken up, one night, I went to her lab,
发现一张字迹潦草的纸 一张表
found a scribbled piece of paper-- a list.
潜在的男朋友必须在既定的日期
Potential boyfriends had to fulfill certain conditions
满足特定的条件 否则就拜拜
by a prearranged date, or else good-bye.
比如说...
Such as...
开始还比较正常
Well, things start off relatively normal:
为她开门
Opening the door for her,
买花 拉椅子...
flowers, putting the seat down...
大概到了... 第八条...
Then, around... number eight...
就变得 呃...
it gets, uh...
怎么了
What?
她知道你拍下这些了吗
Does she know you have these?
知道 她发现时很不高兴
Yeah, she wasn't happy when she found out.
这些都十分...
These are all very...
-具体 -对
- specific. - Yeah.
这些要求对你也适用吗
These ideas apply to you?
不 不
No, no.
我们在一起的时候 还没有这些要求
Those rules weren't in place when we were together.
至少 我觉得没有...
At least, I don't think so...
两个月截止点是怎么回事
And what's with the two-month cut-off?
Abby在毁了她自己
Abby's sabotaging herself.
我以前见过这种情况
I've seen stuff like this before.
我们必须跟她谈谈
We have to talk to her.
不 不 不 不
No! No, no, no!
不 你什么都不能说
No. You cannot say a word.
如果你说了 Abby就知道是我告诉你的了
If you say anything, Abby'll know I told you.
相信我们 Bishop
Trust us, Bishop.
Abby的约会世界就是个大漩涡
The Abby dating world is a vortex
你不会想卷进去的
you do not want to get sucked into.
有时候... 太复杂了
Sometimes... it's complicated.
就让她做自己吧
Just let Abby be Abby.
我整晚都在浏览相关的法律法规
I spent all night looking through relevant statutes.
然后呢
And?
你知道你的所作所为是违法的
And you know what you did was illegal.
你被抓时在往一个女孩的喉咙里
You were caught holding a tracheotomy tube
插气管
in a girl's throat.
她救了两条人命
And she saved two lives.
她所做的是海军训练她去做的事
She did what the Navy trained her to do.
那多少是有帮助的
That's got to count for something.
如果她是陆军或空军的话 是的
If she was in the Army or in the Air Force, yes.
她就会有急救医生的基本证明
She would be EMT-Basic certified.
但海军训练并不归入国家许可
But Navy training doesn't fall under state licensure.
所以我会因为技术细则而坐牢
So I'm going to jail for a technicality?
我帮你的话就不用坐牢了
Not if I can help it.
我想我们最明智的选择就是承认你所做的事
I think that our best move is to admit what you did.
寻求法律帮助
Go after the law itself?
正是 法律并不是要
Exactly. This wasn't intended
惩罚像你这样的人
to prosecute people like you.
我们说明当时的情况
We present our case,
告诉他们你受过什么训练...
tell them about your training...
当你看到三个孩子垂死之际
that you saw three kids dying
你知道自己有能力施救
that you knew that you could help.
并提供你对这起肇事逃逸事故的证词
Throw in your testimony about the hit-and-run.
如果海军和受害者家属能站在你这边
If we can get the Navy and the victims' families on your side,
我们就有机会
we stand a chance.
好的 我来安排
Okay, I'll set it up.
安排什么
Set what up?
老大 不... 不好意思
Boss, I'm... I'm sorry.
他一直在集合厅等你
He was waiting for you in the squad room.
McGee 没关系
McGee, it's all right.
跟McGee走吧
Go with McGee.
Anna有权找个律师
Anna has the right to an attorney.
女士 你了解法律
Ma'am, you know the law.
希望你不会插手这件事
Please tell me you're not going along with this.
我们还在寻找凶手
We're still looking for a killer.
比如说Dave Lancellotti
Like Dave Lancellotti?
你们找错对象了 Gibbs探员
You're barking up the wrong tree, Agent Gibbs.
我了解这个人 我们是同乡
I know the guy; we're all locals.
Dave性子可能比较急 但他不会杀人
Dave may be a hothead, but he's no killer.
他是个失踪的急性子
He's a hothead no one has heard from.
听着 警官 我们知道你想要答案
Look, Sergeant, we know that you want answers.
我们也想要答案
We want answers, too.
只是想确保我们没有冤枉好人
Just make sure that we're punishing the right person.
Gibbs
Gibbs.
LoJack软件找到Lancellotti的卡车了
【注：防盗/寻回车辆的软件】
LoJack on Lancellotti's truck just lit up.
知道位置吗
Get a location?
车停着 没有行驶
Parked, not moving.
我想我们找到他了
I think we got him.
过会联系你
I'll call you later.
Anna Dillon怎么办
What about Anna Dillon?
什么怎么办
What about her?
我要你保证
I want your word.
这件事结束后
When this is done,
你不能妨碍我的工作
you let me do my job.
警官 我们都有工作要做
Sergeant, we will all do our jobs.
我也去
I'm coming, too.
皮卡有顶棚
Pickup's got a cap.
难怪Anna以为是辆SUV
Explains why Anna thought it was an SUV.
行动
Let's move.
盯着他 Bishop
Keep your eyes on him, Bishop.
Dave Lancellotti
Dave Lancellotti!
NCIS
NCIS!
看来是我错了
Guess I was wrong.
有麻烦了 Palmer先生
Oh, more trouble, Mr. Palmer?
是Breena 她让我带些牛奶和饼干回去
It's Breena. She's asking me to bring home milk and cookies.
还有辣香肠
And pepperoni.
和金枪鱼
And tuna fish.
我希望她不是要辣香肠味的金枪鱼
I hope she doesn't mean pepperoni flavored tuna fish.
怀孕的这个阶段
Yes, well, strange cravings
有奇怪的生理需求再正常不过了
are very common in this stage of pregnancy.
上个礼拜 她用巧克力牛奶做土豆泥
Last week, she used chocolate milk to make mashed potatoes.
哇 我喜欢
Mmm! I love that.
它让我熬过了寄宿学校的头一年
Got me through my first year of boarding school.
死者身上有什么发现吗
Anything on our dead guy?
可以肯定
Well, suffice to say,
死者被一枪击中太阳穴
a gunshot wound to the temple
对下面的组织造成了毁灭性的伤害
that caused catastrophic damage to the underlying tissue.
我想这就是目的所在
I would think that was sort of the point.
但并不是你推测的原因
But not for the reason you surmise.
看这儿
Here.
我们在受害者的指甲下
We found skin and hair fragments
发现了皮肤和毛发碎片
under the victim's fingernails.
所以他...
So he...
开完枪之后又碰了伤口
touched the wound after the gun went off?
但开枪之后他唯一能做的事就只有
The only thing he could've done after the gun discharged
抽搐
was twitch.
枪伤
The gunshot wound
是被用来掩饰一记对太阳穴的致命打击
was used to cover up a fatal blow to the temple,
很可能是用的金属管或者扳手
probably a metal pipe or a wrench.
Lancellotti先生的死被伪造成了自杀
Mr. Lancellotti's death was made to look like a suicide.
在皮卡后面的工具箱里
There was a wrench in the toolbox
有一个扳手
in the back of the pickup.
既然如此 你最好去
Well, then, I suggest you go
拿给Abby化验
and have Abby test it.
当JB参军的时候 我就知道
I always knew when JB joined the Navy,
他有可能回不来了
there was a chance he wouldn't come back,
但以这样的方式...
but to have it happen this way...
当...
When...
他的母亲去世后
his mother passed away,
他就是我的一切
that boy was all I had.
现在他却走了
Now he's gone.
我们无法想象
We can't begin to imagine
无法想象你所经历的一切 Hicks先生
to imagine what you're going through, Mr. Hicks.
你就是那个人
You're the one?
那个停下来帮忙的人
The one who stopped and helped?
他们说你原来是个医生
They said you used to be a medic?
医护兵
A hospital corpsman.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
Hicks先生
Mr. Hicks...
叫我John
Call me John.
John
John.
我刚到那的时候 JB几乎说不出话了
When I first got there, JB could hardly speak.
但即便如此
But even still,
他所关心的仍是他的朋友们
all he cared about was his friends.
他让我帮助他们
He told me to help them.
先救他们
Help them first.
他自始至终都英勇无畏
He was courageous all the way to the end.
你应该为他骄傲
And you should be proud.
他这一生我都为之骄傲
I was proud of JB his whole life.
是真的吗
Is it true...
你被逮捕了
that you've been arrested?
Anna可能会面临监禁 是的
Anna is facing potential jail time, yes.
什么 这样不对
Well, that can't be right.
她救了
She saved
那些孩子
those kids' lives.
也许是不对
It might not be right,
但那是法律
but it's the law.
Anna需要你的帮助 Hicks先生
Anna needs your help, Mr. Hicks.
尽管提
Say the word.
只要她需要
Whatever she needs.
听说你在扳手上找到DNA了
I heard you found the DNA on that wrench.
没错 两组DNA还有一些血迹
Yep, two samples and some blood.
有人试图清洗干净 但是
Somebody tried to wash it off, but, well,
你懂的
you know.
你真是神勇无敌 太赞了 Abbs
Well, when you're good, you're good, Abbs.
那是自然
That's right.
我已经在扳手的开口处
I already got the results back
找到答案了
on the business end of this baby.
肯定是凶器
Definitely the murder weapon.
我只是在等另一组DNA的配对结果
I'm just waiting on results from the other sample.
就在这会儿了
It should be any second now.
好吧 知道吗 盯着DNA看是不会出结果的
Well, you know, a watched DNA never dings.
我们应该聊会儿天
We should talk.
你想聊什么
What do you want to talk about?
除了Burt
Not Burt.
噢 被这个声音拯救了
Oh, saved by the bell.
好吧
Okay.
匹配的DNA来自海军数据库
DNA match from the Navy database.
-来自海军 -没错 获胜者是...
- From the Navy? - Yep, and the winner is...
我们的车载音响小伙
Our car stereo guy,
又名Bennett Jemaine士官
aka Petty Officer Bennett Jemaine.
被派遣到阿富汗前
Barely made it through basic
勉强通过基地训练
before being shipped out to Afghanistan.
在他当上士官后不久
He was dishonorably discharged
就被不光彩退役了
not long after making petty officer.
海军同伴在他的铺位上发现了毒品 举报了他
Fellow sailor found drugs in his bunk, turned him in.
Hicks下士
Petty Officer Hicks.
老大 你确定堵在这儿是个好主意
Boss, are you sure standing here is such a good idea?
我喜欢
I like it.
有77年Clint Eastwood的风范
【注：著名演员 1977年出演电影《铁手套》】
Very Clint Eastwood circa '77.
你怎么知道他会走这条路
How do you know he'll come this way?
小镇子
Small town.
一条路进 一条路出
One road in, one road out.
-要是他不停怎么办 -他会停的
- What if he doesn't stop? - He'll stop.
你确定
You sure?
最后肯定会停的
Eventually.
NCIS
NCIS!
让我看见你的手
Let me see your hands!
汽车俱乐部
Auto club.
要捎你一程不 Bennett
Need a lift there, Bennett?
你被逮捕了 甜心
You're under arrest, sweetheart.
谢谢
Thanks.
医院打来电话
That was the hospital.
Mary LaFleur的状况有所好转
Mary LaFleur's condition is improving.
过程也许有些漫长
It's gonna be a long road,
但是医生认为她还能再次行走
but doctors think she'll walk again.
那真是个好消息
That's good news.
那 现在Anna怎么样了
So, what happens with Anna now?
仍然是无执照行医
Still practiced without a license.
上次我看的时候 还是违法的
Last time I checked, that is still illegal.
只要还有一线希望
If there's a way to fix it,
Gibbs和Carrie就能找出来
Gibbs and Carrie will find it.
希望如此
Let's hope so.
菜鸟 请我喝一杯呗
Probie, drinks on you?
好哒
Uh, yep.
嘿
Hey.
你看起来不错
You look nice.
谢谢
Thanks.
我和Burt有个约会
I have a date with Burt.
我猜你是要去和他分手
I'm assuming you're gonna break up with him,
因为满两个月了
because of the two-month thing?
McGee
McGee,
拜托不要逼我谈论这件事
please don't make me talk about this.
Abby 听着 你不能因为Burt没有做某件他不知情的事
Abby, look, you can't get rid of Burt for not doing something
就甩了他
he doesn't even know about.
他对你很好
He's been good for you.
是的
He has.
但是 也许
But, I mean, maybe...
当我遇见了对的人
when I meet the right guy,
两个月之期就不再是问题了
then the two-month thing won't matter anymore.
我只想说 给Burt一个缓刑
All I'm saying is give Burt an extension.
你永远不会知道
You never know.
当我们俩谈...
When you and I were...
这两月之期的破事也适用
Did all this stuff apply?
我想我们永远都不会知道了
I guess we'll never know.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
嘿 一切都还好吗
Hey. Is everything okay?
一切都好极了
Everything is great.
晚安 McGee探员
Good night, Agent McGee.
晚安
Good night.
她说她8:00会跟我们联系
She said she'd get in touch by 8:00.
现在才7:55
It's 7:55.
她还没迟到
She's not late yet.
我快急死了
This is killing me.
Carrie是行家
Carrie's a pro.
她会替你争取个好的交易
She'll get you a good deal.
我知道 我知道 我很感激
I know, I know, and I-I appreciate
你们为我做的一切 但是
what you both are doing for me, but...
我的生活悬于一线
my life is on the line.
过来
Come here.
拿着这个
Hold this.
顺着纹理 来回动
With the grain, back and forth.
磨平了 顺着纹理磨
Smooth, always with the grain.
你觉得这样有帮助
You think this will help?
对我有帮助 继续磨
Helps me. Keep sanding.
我一整个晚上都在费尔法克斯县的
I've been at the Fairfax County prosecutor's office
公诉人办公室
all evening.
在我确认正式结果之前
I didn't want to tell you
我不想告诉你
until I was sure it was official.
谈成交易了
We have a deal?
是的
We do.
然后
And?
公诉人撤销了指控
The commonwealth attorney reduced the charges.
你所欠的只有社区服务
All you owe is community service.
什么
What?
怎么办到的
How?
受害者父母 所有人
Victims' parents, all of them,
他们去找了Harper军士
they went to Sergeant Harper.
JB的父亲说你是个英雄
JB's dad said that you were a hero,
你应该被表彰
that you deserved a commendation,
而不是被监禁
not jail time.
哦 天呐
Oh, my God...
太不可思议了
This is amazing.
去上学 Dillon
Go to school, Dillon.
拿到证书
Get certified.
继续帮助别人
Keep helping people.
我要怎么才能感谢你们
What can I do to thank you?
是我们要感谢你 医生
We should be thanking you, Doc.
==GA字幕组==
翻译：小白 米兰伯爵 清欢仰慕者 lynhoo00 补汤
校对：寂静流年 清欢仰慕者 师太 Jzc BDFZer 低落的蓉小张
大主教：补汤
英文字幕：elder_man
-嫁祸给一女人，你真好意思-
-看到JB我就想起谷大-
-Do not do evil in order that good may come-
-Palmer越来越像Duck了-
-NCIS总部的男厕所好危险-
-女律师和Gibbs眉来眼去的，管他什么rule，Gibbs你还是从了吧-
-其实我想Abb和Meg在一起-
-祝Abby幸福~-
-麦小呆简直就是Abby的大家长有木有==！！-
-所以和Abby约会满两个月到底要做什么？！！-